skinit.com 2017-06-27

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to SkinIt.com. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the SkinIt.com Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.

**Why we collect personal information**  
SkinIt.com collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you withconvenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest service, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in market research, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better services and products.

**How We Collect Personal Information**  
We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to make a purchase or request service, or participate in an online survey. In addition, when you complete your online order, we collect and store the information you provide in a secure database. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to identify you so we can retrieve your information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

To save you time and make our web services even easier to use, some areas of the SkinIt.com website allow you to create an "SkinIt.com User Account" using your personal information. Here's how it works: Simply fill out a brief profile - your name and e-mail address - then choose a password for security. The system saves your information and assigns you a personal SkinIt.com User Account. Next time you order something from SkinIt.com, you can simply enter your e-mail address and password - the system will automatically look up the information it needs.

**When We Disclose Personal Information**  
SkinIt.com works with other companies that help us provide products and services to you, and we may provide your personal information to these companies. For example, we give shipping companies this information so they can deliver your products efficiently. The information they receive is for shipping and delivery purposes only.

At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest.

**How we protect your personal information**  
SkinIt.com safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

SkinIt.com uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To place on-line orders with SkinIt.com, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Mozilla Firefox, Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Internet Explorer. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet.

**Collecting Other Personal Information**  
When you browse SkinIt.com's website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse - not even your e-mail address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.

Like many websites, the SkinIt.com website uses "cookie" technology. When you first connect to our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.

Skinit.com also uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) .

**SkinIt.com Commitment to Privacy**  
To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every SkinIt.com employee. SkinIt.com does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.

This website contains links to other sites. SkinIt.com does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via e-mail using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.

© 2017 Skinit Acquisition LLC. All Rights Reserved .
